Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=The Demon=
=الشيطان=
=Episode 13=
=الحلقة 13=
No…
لا…
(Happiness)
(سعادة)
Bow to heaven and earth.
انحني للسماء والأرض.
Bow to this auspicious moment.
انحني لهذه اللحظة الميمونة.
The husband and wife bow to each other.
الزوج والزوجة ينحنيان لبعضهما البعض.
(Fan Awu)
(ملابس المشجعين)
(Shen Qinghe)
(شين تشينغهي)
The ceremony is complete.
تم الانتهاء من الحفل.
Awu,
حسنًا،
from now on, you are my wife.
من الآن فصاعدا أنت زوجتي.
Demon,
شيطان،
face your fate!
واجه مصيرك!
No!
لا!
How could this be?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا؟
Exactly the same.
نفس الشيء تماما.
How can it be exactly the same?
كيف يمكن أن يكون الأمر نفسه بالضبط؟
Could that dream have been
هل كان من الممكن أن يكون هذا الحلم
from a past life of mine?
من حياتي الماضية؟
Qinghe!
تشينغهي!
Save… save yourself…
أنقذ... أنقذ نفسك...
No, I won't!
لا لن افعل ذلك!
I'm not going anywhere!
انا لا اذهب الى اي مكان!
We promised
لقد وعدنا
we would be together forever!
سوف نكون معا إلى الأبد!
Qinghe!
تشينغهي!
May we be together again in another life…
نتمنى أن نكون معًا مرة أخرى في حياة أخرى...
Qinghe…
تشينغهي…
Qinghe!
تشينغهي!
♪Parasol leaves fall♪
♪أوراق المظلة تتساقط♪
♪A lonely shadow under the moon♪
♪ظل وحيد تحت القمر♪
♪A refreshing evening breeze♪
♪نسيمة مسائية منعشة♪
♪Those whispers♪
♪تلك الهمسات♪
♪Still echo♪
♪لا يزال صدى♪
♪In my heart♪
♪في قلبي♪
♪Dim candle, long windy night♪
♪شمعة خافتة، ليلة طويلة عاصفة♪
♪Floral fragrance fills the garden♪
♪عطر الزهور يملأ الحديقة♪
♪Can't shake it from my mind, it all ends in nothingness♪
♪لا أستطيع التخلص من هذا الأمر في ذهني، كل شيء ينتهي إلى العدم♪
♪Troubling me half my life♪
♪يزعجني نصف حياتي♪
♪You're the sleepless wind chime♪
♪أنت جرس الرياح الذي لا ينام♪
♪Stirring all my thoughts♪
♪إثارة كل أفكاري♪
♪You're the shooting star who lights my loneliness♪
♪أنت النجم الساطع الذي ينير وحدتي♪
♪Spring comes, autumn goes♪
♪يأتي الربيع ويذهب الخريف♪
♪Sun and Moon turn in cycles, that unendurable winter♪
♪تدور الشمس والقمر في دورات، هذا الشتاء الذي لا يطاق♪
♪The unmelting ice♪
♪الجليد الذي لا يذوب♪
Qinghe,
تشينغهي,
live on.
استمر في العيش.
♪The scenery I cannot reach♪
♪المناظر الطبيعية التي لا أستطيع الوصول إليها♪
♪You are countless threads, an unbroken dream♪
♪أنت خيوط لا تعد ولا تحصى، حلم غير منقطع♪
♪You are the liquor of sorrow that breaks the heart♪
♪أنت شراب الحزن الذي يكسر القلب♪
♪Drunk yet awake♪
♪سكران ولكن مستيقظ♪
♪Troubling me half my life♪
♪يزعجني نصف حياتي♪
♪You're the sleepless wind chime♪
♪أنت جرس الرياح الذي لا ينام♪
♪Stirring all my thoughts♪
♪إثارة كل أفكاري♪
♪You're the shooting star who lights my loneliness♪
♪أنت النجم الساطع الذي ينير وحدتي♪
♪Spring comes, autumn goes♪
♪يأتي الربيع ويذهب الخريف♪
♪Sun and Moon turn in cycles, that unendurable winter♪
♪تدور الشمس والقمر في دورات، هذا الشتاء الذي لا يطاق♪
♪The unmelting ice♪
♪الجليد الذي لا يذوب♪
♪No matter how far I go, you remain♪
♪مهما ابتعدت، ستبقى♪
♪The scenery I cannot reach♪
♪المناظر الطبيعية التي لا أستطيع الوصول إليها♪
Awu!
أوه!
♪You are countless threads, an unbroken dream♪
♪أنت خيوط لا تعد ولا تحصى، حلم غير منقطع♪
♪You are the liquor of sorrow that breaks the heart♪
♪أنت شراب الحزن الذي يكسر القلب♪
♪Drunk yet awake♪
♪سكران ولكن مستيقظ♪
Awu…
حسنًا…
Dayao.
مع السلامة.
Master.
يتقن.
My time is running out.
وقتي ينفد .
Once I return
بمجرد عودتي
the demon core inside me,
جوهر الشيطان بداخلي،
my life will end immediately.
ستنتهي حياتي على الفور.
She lost a demon core, causing her powers to be unbalanced,
لقد فقدت جوهر الشيطان، مما تسبب في عدم توازن قواها،
and her fear of water even stronger than others of her kind.
وخوفها من الماء أقوى من خوف الآخرين من أمثالها.
That's why she transforms
لهذا السبب تتحول
during rainy days.
خلال الأيام الممطرة.
She is a rare Cat Demon with two demon cores.
إنها شيطانة قطة نادرة ذات نواتين شيطانيتين.
Though she is a demon,
على الرغم من أنها شيطانة،
she carries an extraordinary mission.
إنها تحمل مهمة غير عادية.
And you are destined
وأنت مقدر
to be her tribulation.
أن يكون محنتها.
That's why you sent me to find the demon core.
لهذا السبب أرسلتني للبحث عن جوهر الشيطان.
Not to have her heal me,
لا أريدها أن تشفيني،
but to use my life
ولكن لاستخدام حياتي
to end this disaster.
لإنهاء هذه الكارثة.
My life was given to me by her.
لقد أعطتني حياتي.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
I won't sacrifice Dayao's happiness
لن أضحي بسعادة داياو
for a fleeting moment of pleasure.
لحظة عابرة من المتعة.
Nor will I abandon Moyuan City
ولن أتخلى عن مدينة مويوان
and its people.
وشعبها.
I accept my destiny,
أنا أقبل مصيري،
and I want Dayao
وأنا أريد داياو
to have a peaceful, complete life.
أن أحظى بحياة هادئة ومتكاملة.
Do you intend
هل تنوي
to face this catastrophe
لمواجهة هذه الكارثة
all on your own?
كل ذلك بمفردك؟
You might lose
قد تخسر
everyone close to you.
كل من هو قريب منك.
When that happens,
عندما يحدث ذلك،
you'll be all alone again.
سوف تكون وحيدًا مرة أخرى.
The happiness you long for,
السعادة التي تتوق إليها
your loved ones…
أحبائك…
It's all right.
كل شيء على ما يرام.
I can bear it.
انا استطيع تحمل ذلك.
Shen Wangchen,
شين وانجشن,
I'm giving you one last chance.
سأعطيك فرصة أخيرة.
If you agree to marry me,
إذا وافقت على الزواج مني،
I will use all the power of my court
سأستخدم كل قوة محكمتي
to eliminate the demons causing chaos
للقضاء على الشياطين المسببة للفوضى
in the city.
في المدينة.
I agree.
أنا موافق.
If you continue to be stubborn,
إذا واصلت العناد،
don't blame me for…
لا تلومني على...
You…
أنت…
You agree?
هل توافق؟
Did he say yes?
هل قال نعم؟
Was he speaking to me?
هل كان يتحدث معي؟
Yes.
نعم.
Shen Wangchen,
شين وانجشن,
I love you.
أحبك.
Dayao,
صباح الخير،
I've decided
لقد قررت
to propose to Princess Huaiyang.
للتقدم لخطبة الأميرة هوايانج.
Looks like someone
يبدو وكأنه شخص ما
still doesn't understand the situation.
لا يزال لا يفهم الوضع.
Why are you proposing to her?
لماذا تتقدم لها بطلب الزواج؟
Are you that close now?
هل أنت قريب الآن؟
You shouldn't be
لا ينبغي لك أن تكون
living here anymore.
أعيش هنا بعد الآن.
Pack your things
حزم أغراضك
and return to the fort.
والعودة إلى الحصن.
You…
أنت…
- Mr. Shen… - Young Master…
- السيد شين... - السيد الشاب...
Her Highness has spoken.
لقد تحدثت صاحبة السمو.
Who dares defy her orders?
من يجرؤ على تحدي أوامرها؟
What's gotten into you?
ماذا حدث لك؟
I told you.
أخبرتك.
No one here
لا أحد هنا
can harm me.
يمكن أن يؤذيني.
If you hadn't stopped me, I would have already…
لو لم توقفني لكنت فعلت ذلك بالفعل...
Jiang Li.
جيانغ لي.
Help Chief Fan pack up.
ساعد رئيس المعجبين في التعبئة.
♪I'm fine♪
♪أنا بخير♪
♪I haven't forgotten♪
♪لم أنسى♪
♪Forever♪
♪إلى الأبد♪
♪Together♪
♪معا♪
♪The cold breeze brings sadness♪
♪النسيم البارد يجلب الحزن♪
♪But it knows♪
♪لكنه يعرف♪
♪Unforgettable love that spans across lifetimes♪
♪حب لا يُنسى ويستمر عبر الحياة♪
♪Not afraid♪
♪لا أخاف♪
♪The world's adversities will overcome all obstacles for you♪
♪ ستتغلب مصاعب العالم على كل العقبات من أجلك♪
I'm furious!
أنا غاضب!
I was wrong
لقد كنت مخطئا
about Shen Wangchen!
حول شين وانغشن!
How could he do that to you?
كيف يمكنه أن يفعل ذلك بك؟
♪Dust swirls as we go our separate ways without looking back♪
♪تدور الدوامات الغبارية بينما نسلك طرقنا المنفصلة دون النظر إلى الوراء♪
What's gotten into him?
ماذا حدث له؟
Isn't it obvious?
أليس هذا واضحا؟
I think he's completely obsessed with Princess Huaiyang.
أعتقد أنه مهووس تمامًا بالأميرة هوايانج.
Dayao,
صباح الخير،
let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Let's move on from this mess.
دعونا ننتقل من هذه الفوضى.
We can't leave just yet.
لا يمكننا المغادرة بعد.
There must be a misunderstanding.
لابد أن يكون هناك سوء فهم.
Shen Wangchen said to be patient
قال شين وانغ تشين إنه يجب أن يكون صبورًا
and hear the explanation.
واسمع التفسير.
Explanation?
توضيح؟
What's there to explain?
ماذا هناك لتوضيح؟
Dayao,
صباح الخير،
you're too kind
أنت لطيف للغاية
and too easily used.
ويتم استخدامها بسهولة أيضًا.
You mean he's using me?
هل تقصد أنه يستغلني؟
Yes.
نعم.
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
He's not that kind of person.
إنه ليس هذا النوع من الأشخاص.
Dayao…
مع السلامة…
Your Majesty…
جلالتك…
Enough.
كافٍ.
I'm the chief.
انا الرئيس.
♪Where did I lose my direction?♪
♪أين فقدت اتجاهي؟♪
♪Only emptiness is left♪
♪لم يبق سوى الفراغ♪
♪Restless, sleepless, we part ways♪
♪أرق، بلا نوم، افترقنا♪
♪As sorrow slowly grows within♪
♪كما ينمو الحزن ببطء في الداخل♪
♪Tears can't heal, smiles still ache♪
♪الدموع لا يمكن أن تشفى، والابتسامات لا تزال تؤلم♪
♪Because my heart's with you♪
♪لأن قلبي معك♪
♪Your gaze melted the haze♪
♪نظرتك أذابت الضباب♪
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
♪انتظر عودتك لفترة طويلة♪
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
♪تذكّرني الشمس الغاربة بك♪
♪If the clear sky is torn by storm and rain one day♪
♪إذا تمزقت السماء الصافية بالعاصفة والمطر يومًا ما♪
♪Tears will flow♪
♪الدموع سوف تتدفق♪
♪I will still wait here with no regrets♪
♪سوف أظل أنتظر هنا دون أي ندم♪
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
♪انتظر عودتك لفترة طويلة♪
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
♪تذكّرني الشمس الغاربة بك♪
♪In the amber desert, you turn away with tears in your eyes♪
♪في الصحراء الكهرمانية، تبتعد والدموع في عينيك♪
♪I'll welcome you back in a red dress♪
♪سأرحب بك مرة أخرى في ثوب أحمر♪
♪Waiting forever with no regrets♪
♪الانتظار إلى الأبد دون أي ندم♪